http://www.saplonline.org/content/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Last updated 10/5/20
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page. AWI does not trade, share or sell donors’ addresses or other personal information with any third party for any reason.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on awionline.org or compassionindex.org. On some pages on these sites, you can provide feedback, request further information or materials, or contact government officials or other outside entities to express your opinions. You may be asked, in these cases, to provide some personal information such as the following:
Name
Address
Phone number
Email address
Issue Reported
Note that the website safehavensforpets.org does NOT collect any personal information.
The AWI website also collects “visitor data”—certain other information that cannot be used to identify you personally when you visit our website. This visitor data may include internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, the webpage you were visiting before you came to our website, pages of our website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our website, access times and dates, and other statistics. Visitor data does NOT contain any personally identifiable information (PII).
Like most websites, we also use “cookies” to save some contact information you have previously provided, to better understand how you interact with the website, to gather general visitor information and track visits to our website, and to make the user experience more streamlined. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. PII is not captured in such cookies, nor does AWI use cookies to mine PII. You can always set your browser to warn of cookies being placed, and then choose which cookies you want to accept. Standard browsers also allow you to easily delete cookies currently on your computer.
AWI uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features on our website: Demographics and Interests Reporting, Geography, and Site Behavior. We use this information to help deliver more relevant information to you based on your location, past interactions with our site, and demographic information. We do not store this information in an individually identifiable format, and we do not share this information with third parties. If you wish to opt-out of Google Analytics Advertising Features, you may do so here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself to keep you updated on our work, respond to your inquiries, send you administrative communications, let you know about issues or events we think you’ll be interested in, let you know about opportunities to get involved or take action, and statistically analyze user behavior and activity for research and measurement activities.
We may share aggregated information that does not include PII and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying information and visitor data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your PII.
Finally, we never use or share PII provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above unless specifically agreed to by you or to comply with legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order. We may employ third party companies and individuals to provide services on our behalf, to perform website-related services (such as maintenance services, database management, web analytics, and improvement of the website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our website is used. These third parties have access to your PII only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. When you enter PII, we encrypt the transmission of that information or use SSL [Secure Socket Layer] connections technology. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. In the event of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored PII, we will notify you as quickly as possible via email or conspicuous posting on this website.
Links
The website may contain links to third-party websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that AWI is not responsible or liable for the availability or accuracy of such websites or resources, or the content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. Links to such websites or resources do not imply any endorsement by AWI of such websites or resources or the content, products, or services available from such websites or resources. You acknowledge sole responsibility for and assume all risk arising from your use of any such websites or resources or the content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. Please note: When you click on links to other websites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is not directed to persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without that parent or guardian’s consent, he or she should contact us at awi@awionline.org. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may modify our privacy policy at any time without prior notice and such modification will be effective upon posting to the website. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then-current version of the privacy policy.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call AWI at (202) 337-2332. You are always welcome to email us at awi@awionline.org to request to review/update your personal information, ask us to unsubscribe you from our emails, or ask us to completely delete your information from our records. The link to our privacy policy can always be found at the bottom of our website.
Share This!
Refinement Forum (LAREF)
Signs of Animal Abuse for Child Protection Worker and Others
United States Legislative Information (external link)
Refinement Forum (LAREF)
Signs of Animal Abuse for Child Protection Worker and Others
United States Legislative Information (external link)
